Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, 1918-2006
  - Subseries A: Contact Sheets with Shoot Numbers
    - Demonstration by Service Employees International Union Local 1199 at Democratic National Convention., Jul 12, 1976 - Jul 15, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760141)
    - Democratic National Convention., Jul 16, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760142)
    - Demonstration for Day Care, Brooklyn, New York., Jul 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760143)
    - Ron Tyson and Mike Glick Signing Stockholm Peace Appeal., Jul 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760145)
    - Demonstration by Women Strike for Peace, 8th Avenue and 34th Street, New York, New York., Jul 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760146)
    - Lucy Mahler Mural, Washington Heights school, New York, New York., Jul 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760147)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Demonstration, Mount Sinai Hospital, New York, New York., Jul 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760148)
    - Building Code Violation at Cathedral Parkway Tower (125 West 109th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Aug 3, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760150)
    - Interview with Robert Christman (Administrator, Sydenham Hospital) on Right to Stop Hospital's Closing., Aug 5, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760151)
    - Bronx, New York. Photos by Terry Sanchez., Aug 10, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760152)
    - Demonstration by United Farmworkers, George Washington Bridge, New York, New York., Aug 12, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760153)
    - Demonstration for Puerto Rico. Photos by Terry Sanchez., Aug 26, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760154)
    - Demonstration by Hospital Workers, Harlem Hospital, New York, New York., Aug 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760158)
    - Demonstration for South Africa. Photos by Liz Velez., Sep 6, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760160)
    - Sit-in at Dominican Republic Embassy, New York, New York., Sep 7, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760161)
    - Ted Bassett Birthday Celebration., Sep 19, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760162)
    - Chile Solidarity Emergency Committee, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Enrici Kirberg and Suni Paz pictured., Sep 28, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760163)
    - Demonstration by Metropolitan Council on Housing to Save Sam Burt Houses (Brooklyn, New York)., Sep 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760164)
    - Raleigh, North Carolina., Sep 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760166)
    - Orlando Letelier Memorial Service, New York, New York., Oct 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760170)
    - Herbert Aptheker., Oct 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760171)
    - Demonstration to Save Child Care in New York., Oct 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760172)
    - Gus Hall-Jarvis Tyner Election Rally, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York., Oct 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760173)
    - Demonstration for Housing by HomeFront., Nov 11, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760174)
    - Symphonic Voices of Sugar Hill (musical group)., Nov 26, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760175)
    - South Africa Freedom Day, State Office Building (125th Street and 7th Avenue), New York, New York. Eniceo de Figuereido, Paulo Jorge Manval, Jose Carlos Lobo, Tony Monteiro, Acosta Barthwell and Henry Winston Pictured. Photos by Maxine Orris., Dec 3, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760176)
    - Chilean-American Christmas Celebration., Dec 19, 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760177)
    - Demonstration at Ipi-Tombi (South African play)., Dec 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760179)
    - William L. Patterson Dinner., Dec 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760184)
    - Center for Graphic Arts Opening., 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760192)
    - Kendra Alexander., 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760194)
    - Demonstration to Save Schomburg Library, New York, New York., 1976 (Box 34, Shoot 760195)
    - Amnesty Conference, Toronto, Canada., Jan 29-30, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770001)
    - School and Library Employees Union Local 74 on Strike., Jan 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770002)
    - Housing, Lower East Side, New York, New York., Jan 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770003)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 820 on Strike at Wells Fargo., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770004)
    - Demonstration by National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL) Against Citibank and First National Bank., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770006)
    - Demonstration by New York Coalition Against Inflation and Unemployment Against Budget Cuts., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770008)
    - Daily World Staff., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770011)
    - Chilean Government Representatives Visit New York., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770012)
    - Child Care Discovery Room, 162nd Street and Amsterdam Avenue, New York, New York., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770013)
    - Street Theater., Feb 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770015)
    - Metropolitan Council on Housing., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770016)
    - Demonstration Against Closing of Senior Center., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770017)
    - Demonstration to Keep Martin Luther King, Jr. High School Open., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770023)
    - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Luncheon., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770024)
    - Demonstration for Subways, New York, New York., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770025)
    - Demonstration by Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment, Brooklyn, New York., Mar 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770027)
    - New World Review Luncheon, Americana Hotel, New York, New York. Jessica Smith, Henry Winston, Ricardo Alarcon and Cheddi Jagan pictured., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770029)
    - Demonstration for Palestinian Political Prisoners Held in Israel., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770030)
    - Demonstration for Family Day Care, City Hall, New York, New York., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770032)
    - Gladys Marin Arrives from Chile at John F. Kennedy International Airport, New York, New York. Enrique Kirberg, Roque Ristorucci and James Steele also pictured., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770033)
    - Daily World and Voz del Pueblo Event. Dorothy Robinson, Margaret Pittman, Seymour Joseph and Carl Winter pictured., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770034)
    - Margaret Pittman in Westport, Connecticut., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770035)
    - WBAI-FM Closed because of Labor Dispute., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770037)
    - Youth Waiting for Summer Jobs. Six-thousand Applicants for 300 Positions., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770039)
    - Demonstration Against Budget Cuts, City University of New York., Apr 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770040)
    - Demonstration by Coalition Against Inflation and Unemployment Against Budget Cuts., May 4, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770041)
    - Jobs for Youth Parade, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., May 21, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770042)
    - Gladys Marin, Maria Elena Carrera and Carmen Gloyia Aquayo (Chilean women) Speak Out., May 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770043)
    - Demonstration in Support of Striking J.P. Stevens Workers., May 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770044)
    - Demonstration by National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment, Washington, D.C., Jun 28, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770050)
    - Puerto Rican Day Parade., Jun 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770052)
    - Las Papines (Cuban musical group), New York, New York., Jul 29, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770056)
    - Demonstration by Coalition Against Inflation and Unemployment., Jul 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770058)
    - J.P. Stevens Boycott, New York, New York., Jul 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770059)
    - Petitioning, New York, New York., Aug 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770061)
    - Henry Winston, Fern Winston and Family., Aug 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770062)
    - Puerto Rican Folklorica Festival, New York, New York., Aug 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770064)
    - Demonstration Against International Hotel Evictions, San Francisco, California., Aug 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770065)
    - Demonstration Against Apartheid at Tennis Match., Sep 11, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770066)
    - Daily World Picnic., Sep 11, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770067)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) Convention, Washington, D.C., Sep 16-18, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770068)
    - Alicia Alonso Dances at American Ballet Benefit., Sep 29, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770070)
    - Daily World Staff and Offices., Sep 30, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770071)
    - Roberta "Bobby" Wood (steel worker), Chicago, Illinois., Sep 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770072)
    - United Electrical Workers (UE) Convention, New York, New York., Sep 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770073)
    - Delegation from Soviet Union Hold Press Conference at National Center for Trade Union Action and Democracy (TUAD) and Service Employees International Union Local 1199., Oct 5, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770075)
    - Demonstration Against University of California v. Bakke Decision., Oct 8, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770076)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Convention., Oct 7-10, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770077)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Convention., Oct 7-10, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770078)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Convention. Photos by Ken BeSaw., Oct 7-10, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770079)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Convention. Photos by Tony Velez., Oct 7-10, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770080)
    - Demonstration during Young Workers Liberation League Convention., Oct 7-10, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770081)
    - Charles Spector "Running for Governor," New Jersey., Oct 24, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770086)
    - Demonstration by Housekeepers, Morrisania Community Corporation, Bronx, New York., Oct 25, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770087)
    - Demonstration in Solidarity with South Africa, New York, New York., Oct 26, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770088)
    - Labor Research Association Luncheon., Oct 30, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770090)
    - Puerto Rico., Oct 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770093)
    - Lakeville Teachers on Strike., Oct 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770097)
    - Women for Racial and Economic Equality Conference, Chicago, Illinois., Oct 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770096)
    - Association of Legal Aid Attorneys on Strike., Nov 2, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770098)
    - Demonstration by Vietnam Veterans on Veteran's Day., Nov 11, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770099)
    - Gus and Elizabeth Hall Returning from Moscow., Nov 12, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770101)
    - Sean O'Cionnaith (Sinn Fein leader)., Nov 21, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770104)
    - Henry Winston Returning from Moscow., Nov 27, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770107)
    - Charlene Mitchell at United Nations, New York, New York., Nov 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770110)
    - Demonstration by Taxi Workers Against Leasing Plan, World Trade Center, New York, New York., Dec 9, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770112)
    - Women Miners., Dec 19, 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770115)
    - Israel. Photos by Dan Spector., Dec 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770116)
    - United Mine Workers on Strike, Consolidation Coal Company, Moundsville, West Virginia., Dec 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770118)
    - Candlelight March for Teachers Strike, New Haven, Connecticut., Dec 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770121)
    - Demonstration by Waterbury Teachers Association Against Layoffs and Large Class Size., Dec 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770122)
    - Demonstration Against New Director, Henry Street Settlement House, New York, New York., Dec 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770123)
    - Demonstration in Supprt of Service Employees Interational Union Local 1199 at Kidney Center., 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770135)
    - Cheddi Jagan., 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770139)
    - New York Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression Conference for New York City., 1977 (Box 34, Shoot 770153)
    - Press Conference by United Mine Workers of America., Jan 24, 1978 (Box 34, Shoot 780002)
    - Senior Citizens, South Bronx, New York., Jan 1978 (Box 34, Shoot 780004)
    - Year Against Apartheid Exhibit at United Nations., Jan 1978 (Box 34, Shoot 780005)
    - Demonstration Against Milton Friedman., Dec 1978 (Box 34, Shoot 780112)
    - Demonstration Against Evictions, Brooklyn, New York., 1980 (Box 34, Shoot 806118)
    - Unidentified Event., 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860113)
    - Gus Hall at Unity Center, New York, New York., Nov 23, 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860114)
    - Daily World Staff., 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860116)
    - Demonstration Against Homelessness., 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860117)
    - Demonstration Against United States Interference in Central America., 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860121)
    - Henry Winston Memorial Service., Dec 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860124)
    - Henry Winston Memorial Service., Dec 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860125)
    - Henry Winston Memorial Service., Dec 1986 (Box 34, Shoot 860126)
    - Henry Winston Memorial Service., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870127)
    - Press Conference Against Plant Closings. Participants include Jesse Jackson., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870128)
    - Interview with Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870129)
    - Demonstration Against Trimbec Temps, Incorporated., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870130)
    - United Auto Workers Local 659, Detroit, Michigan., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870132)
    - Demonstration Against Layoffs, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870133)
    - Demonstration Against Colt's Manufacturing., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870136)
    - Demonstration Against Sloan Kettering Hospital, New York, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870143)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870145)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings, Lynn, Massachusetts., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870146)
    - Demonstration for Harold Washington, Unidentified Event (bus trip)., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870148)
    - Demonstration for Harold Washington., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870149)
    - Demonstration in Support of United Food and Commercial Workers and the Lion Writes Theater Group., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870151)
    - Uretek Workers on Strike., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870153)
    - Demonstration Against Health-Tex, Maine and Writers Guild of America on Strike Against CBS., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870154)
    - Unidentified Woman at Lafayette Shores Apartments., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870155)
    - Rally for Communist Party of the United States of America 24th National Convention., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870156)
    - International Women's Day Tribute to Sarah Milgram., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870161)
    - Unidentified Demonstration., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870162)
    - Unidentified Demonstration at Brookdale Hospital Medical Center, New York, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870163)
    - Demonstration to Free John Doherty., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870165)
    - Unidentified Demonstration., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870166)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings, Rally for Peace and Justice in South Africa., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870167)
    - Unidentified Meeting., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870168)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870169)
    - Demonstration Against Tribec Temps, Incorporated., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870170)
    - Graduation Ceremony., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870171)
    - Demonstration by International Ladies Garment Workers Union., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870172)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870173)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America, Detroit, Michigan., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870176)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America, Detroit, Michigan., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870177)
    - Unidentified Event. Participants include Bella Abzug., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870178)
    - Demonstration for Housing., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870179)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870182)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870183)
    - Demonstration for Jobs with Peace, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870184)
    - Demonstration for Jobs with Peace, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870185)
    - Demonstration for Jobs with Peace, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870186)
    - Demonstration for Jobs with Peace, Washington, D.C. Communist Party of the United States of America contingent, 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870187)
    - Demonstration for Jobs with Peace, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870188)
    - Genesis Convention Center (Gary, Indiana)and Goldblatt's Pictured., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870189)
    - Demonstration for Justice and Peace in South Africa and Central America, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870190)
    - Demonstration for Peace and Justice in South Africa and Central America, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870191)
    - Demonstration for Peace and Justice in South Africa and Central America, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870192)
    - Demonstration for Peace and Justice in South Africa and Central America, Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870193)
    - Demonstration for Peace and Justice in South Africa and Central America, Washington, D.C. Communist Party of the United States of America Contingent., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870196)
    - May Day Celebration and Demonstration, Union Square, New York, New York., May 1, 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870197)
    - May Day Celebration and Demonstration, Union Square, New York, New York., May 1, 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870198)
    - Demonstration by National Congress for Puerto Rican Rights at Holiday Inn., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870199)
    - First Anniversary of People's Daily World., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870200)
    - Demonstration for Tenants' Rights, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870202)
    - Unidentified Group (delegation?)., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870203)
    - Hearings to Renew Charter for Citywide Welfare Rights Committee at New York City Charter Review Commission., May 7, 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870204)
    - Demonstration Against Plant Closings., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870205)
    - Opening Ceremony, Museum of African American History, Boston, Massachusetts., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870206)
    - Press Conference for L'Eggs Mini Marathon., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870210)
    - Demonstration Against Evictions., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870217)
    - Brooklyn Arms Hotel, Brooklyn, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870218)
    - Demonstration for Benjamin Linder, Nicaragua., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870219)
    - Demonstration Against Apartheid., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870242)
    - Demonstration Against Apartheid., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870243)
    - Demonstration Against Homelessness., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870249)
    - Demonstration for Benjamin Linder, Nicaragua., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870252)
    - Unidentified People., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870255)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 1038 Locked Out of WedTech., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870256)
    - [Soviet Union]., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870260)
    - Unidentified Women., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870261)
    - Demonstration Against Apartheid., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870262)
    - Demonstration for Equal Rights Amendment., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870263)
    - Demonstration for Equal Rights Amendment., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870264)
    - Demonstration by Save Our Sons And Daughters (SOSAD)., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870266)
    - Signing Petitions at Kenneth W. Clement Center for Family Health Care., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870267)
    - Demonstration for Univision (television channel)., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870271)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870272)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870280)
    - Unidentified Woman and Child., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870282)
    - Unidentified Meeting., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870284)
    - Unidentified Man and Woman., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870292)
    - March to Free the Puerto Rico 15 and New England Walk for Nuclear Disarmament., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870294)
    - March to Free the Puerto Rico 15 and New England Walk for Nuclear Disarmament., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870295)
    - Demonstration Against Apartheid., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870298)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870299)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870300)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870301)
    - Labor Day Parade., Sep 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870306)
    - Labor Day Parade., Sep 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870307)
    - Demonstration Against Military Aid to Central America., Sep 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870308)
    - Demonstration Against Military Aid to Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870310)
    - AFL-CIO COPE Picnic., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870309)
    - Demonstration by Substitute Teachers., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870316)
    - Demonstration for El Salvador. Photos by Carl Morgen., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870324)
    - Demonstration Against United States Aid to Contras., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870328)
    - Demonstration Against United States Aid to Contras., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870329)
    - Demonstration Against Racism, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870332)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870333)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870334)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America 24th National Convention., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870335)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America 24th National Convention., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870336)
    - Puerto Rican Celebration., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870337)
    - Jesse Jackson Election Campaign Rally., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870338)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870342)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870343)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870344)
    - C. F. Hamilton House, New York, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870345)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America. Brian Willson pictured., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870346)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870347)
    - Communications Workers of America on Strike., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870352)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in Central America., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870354)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870355)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870356)
    - Demonstration for Education, Unidentified Woman., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870357)
    - Peace Fair, Brooklyn, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870360)
    - Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870365)
    - Demonstration for El Salvador, Unidentified Man., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870366)
    - Demonstration Against United States Intervention in El Salvador., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870367)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 1199 Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870368)
    - Demonstration Against Staten Island Nuclear Homeport., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870369)
    - Demonstration Against Staten Island Nuclear Homeport., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870370)
    - Veterans Day Parade. Veterans for Peace and Gay Veterans Association Contingents., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870377)
    - Scenes in New York, New York., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870379)
    - United States Peace Council Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870381)
    - Inquiring Photographer., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870383)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870386)
    - Demonstration for Nuclear Disarmament, Detroit, Michigan., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870404)
    - Unidentified Event, Washington D.C. (Veteran's encampment?)., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870405)
    - Group of Unidentified Men., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870406)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870407)
    - Unidentified Event., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870411)
    - Demonstration Against Chevron., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870410)
    - Inquiring Photographer, 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870413)
    - Unidentified Event. Photos by Virginia Lerner., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870415)
    - Rally for Living Wage., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870416)
    - African American Members of United Auto Workers., 1987 (Box 34, Shoot 870417)
    - Portraits of Unidentified Individuals., 1988 (Box 34, Shoot 880419)
    - Katya Komisaruk "White Rose," Sentenced to 5 Years. Photos by Chuck Idelson., Jan 13, 1988 (Box 34, Shoot 880420)
    - Distributing People's Daily World. Photos by Mike Giocondo., Jan 13, 1988 (Box 34, Shoot 880421)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Rally, New York, New York. Photos by Joy., Jan 19, 1988 (Box 34, Shoot 880422)